You seem awfully composed.
Of course I do. We still have time.
What did you expect me to do? Give up?
Now, if you're done making small talk,
get back to work,
you slow coach.
Whoops. Silly me.
Good grief.
Why, what have we here?
It looks like plans
for the renovation of city hall.
Renovation?
Yes. A lightning strike caused a fire
just before your execution, and—
Oh, I beg your pardon!
Never mind that.
I don't remember the day of my execution.
You don't?
No, not a thing.
Wait. That's not quite true.
I recall an executioner gave me a fruit
drink before they shackled my hands.
That's it!
I don't remember a thing
after that drink.
Before your execution, they must've given
you that sedative that calms your mind.
It's made from a rare fruit.
Tales tell of crossing the flow of time
for those who consume it.
The flow of time?
Oh? What's this?
A tunnel under Saint Mark's Square?
What a perfect place to conceal hostages.
I'm impressed. Alert the Royal
Security Force at once.
My lady's wish is my command.
I'll be right back!
This time,
I really will show them all that I shall
be the one with the last laugh.
What's this? Have you
come to finish me off?
If I really wanted to kill you,
you'd be dead by now.
I see.
I was dreaming...
Remember I slipped out of the palace to
see popular street performers in the city?
A boy picked my pocket on the way home.
But you caught him right away,
and you said to him...
Whatever your reasons, you should never
live a life you can't be proud of.
I couldn't believe
how upstanding you were.
Was that all an act too?
Of course it was.
I was just parroting Cess.
Cess?
Cici!
You know, Enrique, I've always
despised how careless you are.
But...
just for today, I'll commend you for it.
Cecilia?
Help!
Why, Crown Princess.
I heard a commotion at the royal villa.
Is something the matter?
As it happens, the crown prince is unwell.
The execution is today.
We don't want him dying on us.
Don't worry.
I think it's just one of his fits.
I hope so.
It's time.
What's this?
Merely a fruit drink.
Lord Hamsworth?
The church has prepared
this for you today.
I've received permission to bear witness.
R-Right.
A certain lady told me to see that
you don't take any strange drinks.
A certain lady?
I've been told to move the hostages.
Didn't they notify you?
No, I haven't heard anything.
That's odd.
One down.
Two down.
Your Royal Highness...?
Go straight down the righthand tunnel,
and you'll find an exit to the square.
Didn't you hear me?
Just hurry up and...
go!
What are you playing at?
I couldn't help it, could I?
What?
As I said, I couldn't help it.
There's nothing we can do.
We were bound to lose from the start.
Indeed, that woman...
Scarlett Castiel...
changed fate completely.
Where is the prince?
Who the hell would tell
a scumbag like you?
Fire.
Now...
it's finally over.
Right, Cess?
Did I manage... to do
the right thing in the end?
Whose voice did you want to hear?
I guess even I've lost my edge.
You did it!
That's my Cici!
Cess...
Cici.
Come on.
What do you know?
I can hear her.
She was there all along...
if I'd listened hard enough.
Where are we?
I can see the tower!
We're near Saint Mark's Square!
Look!
You know her, Uly?
Yup!
We're pulling out. Find the prince.
Hi there...
Assistant Comptroller May.
What are you doing here?
You could say the goddesses led us here.
Though their guidance came
by way of an old pig.
Now, I'll give you a choice.
Die now or die later.
'Course, you're a dead man either way.
We're out of time.
Constance...
It's just like ten years ago.
Traitor!
You demon!
Have you no shame?!
Stop that racket!
Honestly, what's wrong with you all?
And people wonder
why I loathe little brats!
Really, Audrey. Such a foul mouth.
Don't be silly, Miriam.
Audrey has bad hearing
and a bad attitude.
Constance Grail is innocent!
Please! Please stop the execution!
Kate!
We have testimony from a girl
who was in Pamela Francis's entourage!
Here! Go on and read it!
Mylene...
Please listen!
I'm—
Constance Grail!
For the crimes of abducting a foreign
prince and plotting insurrection,
you will hereby be beheaded by the sword!
I won't regret a thing.
I refuse to!
Stop right there!
Your Lordship...
This execution is null and void!
The prince is right here!
I am Ulysses Faris, seventh prince
of the Kingdom of Faris.
My abductors hailed from
my homeland of Faris!
That woman had nothing to do with it!
Nonsense!
I don't know who you are!
What's to show you're the real prince?!
Who stands before you is none other than
His Royal Highness Prince Ulysses!
Kendall!
That was fast.
I drove my old bones hard
to make it on horseback.
Here.
This is a record of the
recent council's decision.
I'm amazed you pushed it
through so quickly.
Prince Theophilis put in
a word on our behalf,
but I believe King Ernst's visit
was the deciding factor.
Given that he came at the behest
of the "captive" third princess,
guilty parties doubtless feared
SECOND PRINCE OF FARIS
RODERICK
that you already had
an alliance with Adelbide.
I'll have to thank Allie
for standing in for me.
Yes. Now, the temple has
given its approval as well.
You need only add your own signature.
Will this do?
Allow me to reiterate my delight that
Your Royal Highnesses are both unharmed.
Royal... Highnesses?
Indeed.
I am Alexandra Faris,
legitimate heir to the throne of Faris,
and, as of now, her new sovereign.
N-New sovereign?
You're not hurt, are you?
N-No.
You look a little red.
I... I'm fine!
L-Look, see?!
Her, the queen?
This can't be...
Give it up.
We know about your ties to Rufus May.
He's already in custody.
It's over.
We're sealing off the square!
There won't be any execution!
Damn it all!
This wasn't supposed to happen.
I need you to let me restrain you.
Don't think you've won!
Connie!
Hurry! Run!
Connie...
Connie!
No! Someone help me!
No!
Scarlett!
Remember well, Constance Grail.
A hero always enters fashionably late.
Scarlett!
Honestly, look at all the trouble
you've put me to.
The nerve of you, Connie.
Scarlett?!
So I have no doubt that once you feel
your revenge is complete,
you will return to the gods' side.
No.
No, no, no!
Scarlett!
What an awful face
you're making, silly Connie.
Really, girl, why do I put up with you?
You're not much to look at, you're timid,
you can't keep a secret,
you're silly, you're foolish,
and you don't listen
to a thing people tell you.
But you know...
I love you, Constance Grail.
Scarlett!
Get out.
A dream?
Did I dream all of that?
If so, that future
will never come to pass.
It was all an illusion.
I can't bear it...
For those days, those moments,
to never be...
Anything but that!
I can't be executed like this
and have that be the end!
Tales tell of crossing the flow
of time for those who consume it.
That's right.
Then I need only make
that future a reality.
And to do so...
Of course.
A curse on you.
A curse on you. A curse on you,
Scarlett Castiel.
If it makes that dream the future,
if it makes those days truth,
then abandon shame and reputation
and rise again as a vengeful ghost!
A curse upon you all!
I have no idea whether this
is the right thing to do.
You fiend!
Even so, I'm certain...
I'm sure...
There she is!
It will be all right now.
There's nothing to be afraid of.
After all...
I'll be waiting for you
at the Grand Merillian.
I know that you'll find me again.
Two months have flown by
since you went away.
How have you been there?
The succession dispute
in Faris has been settled,
and Alexandra made it through
her coronation without incident.
With that, we've averted
this war once and for all.
Meanwhile, Crown Princess Cecilia
lost her life that day.
It seems she fell to gunfire letting
Lucia and Prince Ulysses escape.
Even more people have been arrested,
including the mastermind, Rufus May,
and his highborn conspirators.
Pamela's testimony was judged false,
and she keeps attempting to escape the
hospital where she's getting treatment.
Also...
the events of ten years ago
have now come to light.
Translation:
William Varteresian
I have good news on that front.
Scarlett, they've finally
cleared your name.
Subtitle Timing:
Edgar Cruz
Subtitle Editing:
Riley Dalton
At the same time, they can hardly
make public the whole truth of your case.
Quality Check:
SMR
Translation Check:
Sriram Gurunathan
A little embellishment has made
the poisoning part of Daeg Gallus's plot.
Both Mylene and Kate
have started down their own paths.
Lucia was safely reunited
with Lady Abigail,
and I hear she's started corresponding
with Prince Ulysses.
Without Scarlett Castiel around,
my days are quiet, peaceful, and...
a little bit dull.
So allow me to say one last thing...
Silly Scarlett.
Randolph.
Yes?
I was only calling your name.
Only calling my name? Is that so?
It is.
Connie.
Yes? What is it?
I was only calling your name.
Why, if it isn't Miss Grail.
Lord Hamsworth.
Thank you for having me here today.
No thanks necessary.
Welcome to my exhibition.
Is something the matter?
Oh, something about
a stray dog in the garden.
What are the guards doing?
I'll go check on it.
W-Well, then...
I-I'll go with you!
Wait, he's not here.
It's your fault... All your fault...
P-Pamela?
It's your fault.
If you were gone...
If only...
If only you were gone!
Someone...
Someone save me!
Help!
Very well.
I'll help you.
Clumsy as ever, I see.
But how...?
Why, when I stopped to think about it,
I realized I hadn't avenged
myself on anyone.
The thought made me positively livid!
I saw a white light, but I turned back
to avenge myself properly!
You can't be serious...
I saved you, so you've no right to refuse.
Listen well, Constance Grail.
You will spend the rest of your life
ensuring that I have my revenge.
Right.